Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - US Dept. of Labor
    - Aptitude Test Battery Technical Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Misc. Technical Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Aptitude Test Battery Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - Technical Reports, 1969-1975 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Restricted Files
    Conditions Governing Access
    Files are restricted until 2048.
    - Files containing student information, circa 1965-1972 (Box 171)
- Additional material, ARCH-2007-276
  - Nobel Prize, 1956 (Box 1)
  - IEEE Medal of Honor, 1980 (Box 1)
  - IEEE Medal, 1973 March (Box 1)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2008-315
  - Emmy Shockley Audiocassettes, circa 1991-1995; 6 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Photographs, articles, clippings, 1968-1998 (Box 2)
  - The Nurse and the Mental Patient, by Morris Schwartz and Emmy Lanning Shockley, 1956 (Box 2)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2008-337
  - Murray M. Silver telephone conversation, 1984; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Silver, Heston, Shockley telephone conference, 1984 Jan 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Silver, Richard J. Herrnstein, 1984 May 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)